weatherbell.com 2014-05-18

# Privacy Policy

  **Refund Policy**.  All sales are final upon processing. Subscription services will be billed to the credit card on file every 30 days and are non-refundable once processed. Cancellation of a WeatherBELL Analytics subscription must be made in advance of the billing date by visiting the Account page at [www.weatherbell.com/account/edit](http://www.weatherbell.com/account/edit) and clicking on the button labeled “Cancel Subscription”.

**Privacy Policy**.  This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by WeatherBELL Analytics LLC. 

Sometimes, we may post product specific privacy notices to explain our products in more detail.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or write to us or email us at:

**WeatherBELL Analytics LLC** **  
Attn:   **Privacy Policy  
17th Floor  
555 Fifth Ave  
New York, NY 10017**  
**USA**  
**info@weatherBELL.com****

**What We Collect About You.**  We collect information on the WeatherBELL Analytics Sites during the registration process and through your use of the WeatherBELL Analytics Sites for business purposes that will allow us to better and more efficiently serve you. Some uses WeatherBELL Analytics makes of this information are processing and verifying subscriptions, billing, and providing you with up-to-date information on the newest WeatherBELL Analytics products. Third parties, providers, advertisers and vendors (hereinafter "Providers") may be utilized by WeatherBELL Analytics in conjunction with the operation of the WeatherBELL Analytics Sites and the products, services, and advertising related to them. These Providers may also collect information.

You may be asked to provide information that personally identifies you or allows WeatherBELL Analytics and/or its Providers to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you are asked to register for fee-based services, although some free products and services may also request or require registration. You may be asked to provide personally identifiable information such as your name, address, email address and billing information (collectively 'Personally Identifiable Information' or 'PII'), as well as select a username and password (if one is not selected for you by WeatherBELL Analytics).

To the extent unique information, which is not in itself PII, such as personal profile, anonymous identifier(s), demographic information, behavioral information, browser identifiers, session information, device type, carrier provider, unique device ID, UUID/UDID, carrier user ID, web sites visited, IP address and traffic data, is associated with PII, then such unique information shall NOT be considered PII, but shall be considered User Data. Additionally, PII does NOT include information that is collected anonymously (i.e. without identification of the individual user) or demographic or behavioral information that is not connected to or correlated with an identified individual.

**Cookies.**  When you visit WeatherBELL Analytics, we send one or more cookies to your computer or other device. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences.

**Security.**  Anytime a credit card is requested for processing orders through the WeatherBELL Analytics Sites, the user transaction containing the credit card information may be encrypted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. SSL provides strong encryption to all digital information as it crosses the Internet. While on a secure page, such as on order forms, the lock button on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked or open when you are just surfing or in other areas of the Site.

**Password Security Access to certain portions of the WeatherBELL Analytics Sites are password-protected so that you and only you will have access to the Site as a subscriber.**  It may be necessary for WeatherBELL Analytics, its employees, contractors or Providers working on behalf of WeatherBELL Analytics to access the Site using your subscriber information to provide you with support or to perform certain maintenance tasks. This access happens on an as-needed basis only.

**Electronic Registration.**  When you access or install a new product or service, you may be asked to register electronically. Your registration information will be merged with any information you have already provided ('Profile'). If you have not previously registered within the WeatherBELL Analytics Sites, a Profile may be created for you from your product registration information. If you have not already registered by giving us your PII, you will be asked to do so to ensure that only you can access the product or services. Upon satisfactory completion of your registration information, WeatherBELL Analytics authorizes users to access and use the WeatherBELL Analytics Sites and its products and services subject to the Terms & Conditions and this Privacy Statement. User shall maintain the confidentiality of any user name and password. If there is a breach of the confidentiality of a password or user name assigned to user, or any breach of security through user's account, then user shall so notify WeatherBELL Analytics' customer assistance center immediately by contacting WeatherBELL Analytics at info@weatherBELL.com

**Log information.**  When you access WeatherBELL Analytics services via a browser, application or other client our servers automatically record certain information. These server logs may include information such as your web request, your interaction with a service, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your account.

**User communications.**  When you send email or other communications to WeatherBELL Analytics, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. We may use your email address to communicate with you about our services.

**Vendors and Third Party Providers.**  To make the WeatherBELL Analytics Sites more valuable to our customers and our visitors, we may offer some products, services or features in conjunction with Providers. In some instances, our Providers may have the same access to your PII as we do. Their use of the information will be subject to the terms of their respective privacy policies or statements, which you may find on their websites.

In addition to the above, we may use the information we collect to:

  * Provide, maintain, protect and improve our services (including advertising services) and develop new services; and  

  * Protect the rights or property of WeatherBELL Analytics or our users.

If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

WeatherBELL Analytics processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America.

**Information Sharing**

**TERMS FOR SHARING PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION** :

In special circumstances, WeatherBELL Analytics may opt to access or disclose PII when there is reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating WeatherBELL Analytics' Terms & Conditions, this Privacy Statement, any applicable End User License Agreement, Provider or Subscription Terms, or when there is reason to believe an individual may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) WeatherBELL Analytics' rights or property, other WeatherBELL Analytics Site users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. WeatherBELL Analytics may then opt to disclose or access PII in good faith in circumstances where the law requires it, and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve the WeatherBELL Analytics Sites and our products and services. WeatherBELL Analytics may also be requested to disclose PII to law enforcement authorities or as may be required by court-ordered subpoena.

WeatherBELL Analytics is in the business of providing and hosting weather information products, services, and other related products and services as a service to our users. As such, User Data is also considered, a 'customer list', and as such, is a valuable asset to any company subject to legal protection and regulation under federal and state laws as a property interest. Accordingly, User Data will be subject to all customary rights and protections afforded to property owners under these laws. Such rights customarily include the right to transfer the information during the sale of assets to or merger with third parties, and to routinely share such information with affiliates of WeatherBELL Analytics.

Excepting PII collected during the purchasing or registration process, User Data may be used by WeatherBELL Analytics or Providers to, among other things, retrieve or create the product or service that you have requested or for such business purposes as WeatherBELL Analytics and/or its providers may determine in their sole discretion, without resort to a reasonableness standard. Please be advised that this User Data may be stored by WeatherBELL Analytics or its Providers as 'preferences' or otherwise and used without restriction. Further, all information submitted is and becomes the exclusive property of WeatherBELL Analytics and by submitting material to WeatherBELL Analytics, you accept responsibility for its accuracy, appropriateness and legality.

If WeatherBELL Analytics becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transactions and provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Enforcement.   **WeatherBELL Analytics adheres to the US Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, Access and Enforcement, and is registered with the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Safe Harbor Program.

WeatherBELL Analytics regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. When we receive formal written complaints, it is WeatherBELL Analytics’ policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between WeatherBELL Analytics and an individual.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes). We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.
